http://www.insurancecouncilinc.com/privacy/

Home > Privacy Policy
Insurance Council
Home PageMake a PaymentRefer a FriendJoin Our NewsletterCalculatorsInsurance GlossaryFree ReportsOur LocationsEmployee DirectoryContact UsAbout UsPrivacy Policy
Automobile
Automobile Insurance HomeAuto Insurance QuoteRequest ID Card for Auto PolicyRequest Declaration and Coverages Page for Auto PolicySend Declaration and Coverages Information to Lien HolderAdd Vehicle to Existing Auto PolicyRemove Vehicle from Existing Auto PolicyAdd Driver to Existing Auto PolicyRemove Driver from Existing Auto PolicyAuto Accident Claim
Homeowners
Homeowners Insurance HomeHomeowners Insurance QuoteRequest Declaration and Coverages for Existing Homeowners Insurance CoverageProperty Loss Claim Form
Motorcycle
Motorcycle Insurance HomeMotorcycle Insurance QuoteRequest ID Card for Motorcycle PolicyRequest Declaration and Coverages Page for Motorcycle PolicyAdd Motorcycle to Existing PolicyRemove Motorcycle from Existing PolicyAdd Driver to Existing Motorcycle PolicyRemove Driver from Existing Motorcycle PolicyMotorcycle Accident Claim
Business & Commercial
Business & Commercial Insurance HomeCommercial Auto Insurance QuoteRequest ID Card for Commercial Auto PolicyRequest Declaration and Coverages Page for Commercial Auto PolicyAdd Vehicle to Existing Commercial Auto PolicyRemove Vehicle from Existing Commercial Auto PolicyAdd Driver to Existing Commercial Auto PolicyRemove Driver from Existing Commercial Auto PolicyGeneral Liability Quote FormRequest General Liability Certificate of InsuranceCommercial Auto Accident ClaimBusiness Owners (BOP) Quote FormBuilders RiskLiquor Liability Quote FormWorkers Compensation Quote
Bonds
Bonds HomeBond Request Form
Farm
Farm Insurance HomeFarm Quote Request
Recreational Vehicle
Recreational Vehicle Insurance HomeRecreational Vehicle Insurance QuoteRequest ID Card for Recreational Vehicle PolicyRequest Declaration and Coverages Page for Recreational Vehicle PolicyAdd Recreational Vehicle to Existing PolicyRemove Recreational Vehicle from Existing PolicyAdd Driver to Existing Recreational Vehicle PolicyRemove Driver from Existing Recreational Vehicle Policy
Flood
Flood Insurance HomeFlood Quote FormRequest Declaration and Coverages Page for Existing Flood Insurance CoverageFlood Property Loss Claim Form
Other
Other Insurance HomePolicy Review Request
Make a fast, secure payment now!
Privacy Policy
Web site Privacy Policy for Insurance Council.
This notice describes our privacy policy (“Notice”). By visiting our Web Site
(“Web Site”), you are accepting the practices described in this Notice.
ARTICLE I– PRINCIPLES:
Section 1.01 -- Principles: We may gather and use information as follows:
(1) Notice: We may gather and use information as follows:
(a) Volunteered Information: We will receive and store any information you
enter on the Web Site or give us in any other way that personally identifies
you to improve your experience at the Web Site, to get a better general
understanding of the type of individuals visiting the Web Site, and to enable
us to contact you when needed. Typically you will provide information on
the Web Site for the purchase of products or services or when you submit
comments or questions for review by us.
(b) Automatic Information: To enable us to provide content that users need and
desire, we collect aggregated site-visitation statistics using cookies. A
Cookie is simply a small data file we place on your computer’s hard drive when
you first visit the Web Site (“Cookie”). This file contains a unique number
that helps us identify you when you return to the Web Site. Cookies are
employed by thousands of web sites to enhance users’ web viewing experience.
Cookies can neither damage user files nor can they read information from users’
hard drives. We combine all usage information provided by such Cookies and we
do not monitor your use of the Web Site. Allowing us to create a Cookie on your
hard drive will not give us or any other site access to the rest of your
computer’s hard drive, and only we will be able to read the Cookie that the Web
Site creates.
(c) Information Use: We use information for personal identification; to get a
better general understanding of the type of individuals visiting the Web Site;
to respond to your requests for purchases, comments, or questions; to improve
your experience at the Web Site; to collect aggregated site-visitation
statistics; and to alert you to product enhancements, special offers, updated
information, and other new services from us. We also use information to alert
you of subscription renewal discounts, to automatically renew your subscription
and advise you of upcoming service offerings and events.
We may disclose information to third parties, or disclosing
customer lists to commercial or charitable users thereof. Disclosure for such
purposes is limited to your name, company, position, address, phone and fax
numbers, and web site and email addresses. If you do not wish to have such
information disclosed, please let us know by contacting us
. To enable us to process your request, please include your name and address.
Once properly notified, we will remove your name from the lists and disclosures
as soon as we practicably can in the course of normal business practices.
When you order products or services from us, we ask for your credit card number
and billing address. We use this information only to bill you for the products
or services you order at that time and for no other purpose. Annual
subscriptions are payable on the purchase date of the Subscription and renew
automatically each anniversary unless canceled in writing thirty days in
advance of each anniversary date.
Any user questions or comments submitted to us may become available in the
public sections of the Web Site, including a section entitled “Frequently Asked
Questions,” immediately after such questions or comments are submitted to us.
If we publicize any user questions, such questions will not contain facts that
identify the user or the specific parties involved. We also reserve the right
to use any user comments submitted to us for promotional purposes and by
submitting such comments to us you agree that we may do so.
We may release any user information if required to comply with law; to enforce
or to apply the Web Site Terms and Conditions; or under the good faith belief
that disclosure is otherwise necessary or advisable including, without
limitation, to protect the rights, properties, or safety of us or our users.
(2) Choice: We give you a choice as to the type and amount of private
information we have, as follows:
(a) Volunteered Information: You can always choose not to provide certain
information to us. If you choose not to provide personal information, you can
still use many parts of the Web Site. However, you will not be able to purchase
products and services and you will not be able to take advantage of many of our
features. If you have previously provided certain information to us and you
desire to remove such information from our databases, or if you do not wish for
your information to be disclosed to third parties, you may contact
us to remove such information.
(b) Automatic Information: Most web browsers automatically accept Cookies, but
if you prefer, you can edit your browser options to block Cookies in the
future. The “Help” portion of the toolbar on most browsers will explain how you
can prevent your browser from accepting new Cookies, how to set the browser to
inform you when you receive a new Cookie, or how to reject Cookies altogether.
(3) Access: We provide you with the ability to ensure that your personal
information is correct and current. You may review and update your personal
information by contacting us. For security
purposes, we require user verification via user’s user name and password to
receive personal information.
(4) Security: We protect the security of your personal information. We takes
steps to protect your data from loss, misuse, alteration, destruction, or
unauthorized access. We use sophisticated security technologies to secure
users’ ordering information, user name, and password. We encrypt users’
ordering information, user name, and password (including users’ credit card
account number) using Secure Socket Layer (“SSL”) technology. SSL is a proven
coding system that lets your browser automatically encrypt, or scramble, data
before you send it to us. To support this technology, users must have an
SSL-capable browser. SSL is one of the safest encryption technologies
available. While we use such sophisticated security technology to secure users’
ordering information, user name, and password, we cannot guarantee that any
electronic commerce is totally secure.
Section 2.01 -- User Safeguards: You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy
of your user name, password, and any account information. It is important for
you to be responsible and protect your user name, password, and computer
against unauthorized users. It is important to sign off when you have completed
using a computer accessible by others.
Section 3.01 -- Children: We do not sell products for children. Users of the Web
Site must be at least eighteen years old. If a child has provided us with
personal information, that child’s parent or guardian should contact
us to delete such information from our records.
Section 4.01 -- Third Party Web Sites: Please be aware that the Web Site may
have links to third party web sites that may collect personally identifiable
information about you. When you click on one of these third party links, you
are entering another web site for which we have no responsibility. This Notice
does not cover the information practices or policies of such third party web
sites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of all such web sites
since their privacy policies may be materially different from our Notice.
Section 5.01 -- Agreement and Modification: By using and accessing the Web Site
you indicate that you have read and understand this Notice and you consent to
the collection and use of information by us in the manner explained in this
Notice. This Notice and the Web Site Terms and Conditions, including without
limitation, provisions covering limitations on damages, arbitration of
disputes, and the application of Texas law govern any dispute over privacy. By
using and accessing the Web Site you agree to indemnify us for any and all
third party claims resulting from your breach of this Notice or the Web Site
Terms and Conditions. If you have any questions or concerns about your privacy
at the Web Site, please contact us. If you do not
accept this Notice, do not access and use the Web Site. We may revise this
Notice at any time without notice by updating this Notice. Any modifications in
the way we use personal information will be provided in future updates of this
Notice so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it,
and under what circumstances we disclose such information. Modifications will
be effective immediately and will be available on the Web Site. You should
visit this web page periodically to review the Notice. User accepts any such
modifications to this Notice by continued use of the Web Site after such
modifications are made.
Section 6.01 -- Please be aware that Google Analytics Advertising Features may be tracking visitor data on this website. Google Analytics may use cookies to collect Demographics and Interest Reporting data, which is used to get a better general understanding of the type of individuals visiting the Web Site; to collect aggregated site-visitation statistics; and to improve marketing initiatives, such as display and remarketing advertising. This information will not be sold to third parties, and the data collected through Google Analytics Advertising Features - including Demographics and Interest Reporting - is not personally identifiable. If you'd like to opt-out of Google Analytics Advertising Features tracking, click here.
